<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SantaElena</string>
    <string name="SantaElena">Santa Elena Antioquia</string>
    <string name="mensaje">Sports, nature, breathing fresh air and more, 40 minutes from Medellin city, </string>
    <string name="inicio">Home</string>
    <string name="hoteles">Hotels</string>
    <string name="bares">Bars</string>
    <string name="turisticos">Tourist Activities</string>
    <string name="acerca">About...</string>
    <string name="demo">Demographic Information</string>
    <string name="tiMagica">MONTAÑA MÁGICA</string>
    <string name="tMagica">Montaña Magica is an integral farm that provides lodging, spa, restaurant
        and environmental education services. Our farming, handmade, eating, teaching and housing
        products are based on permaculture and sustainable development principles\nWeb Site:
        www.spalamontanamagica.com \nContact:(57+4) 566 9241 \nVereda Piedra Gorda</string>
    <string name="tiMahuampa">CASA DE MONTAÑA MAHUAMPA</string>
    <string name="tMahuampa">Over the high montains that is divided San Nicolas’ Valley and Aburra’s
        Valley, the magic, waving meseta of Santa Elena rises and above impressive San Nicolas  is
        The Mahuampa hostal, place where is possible to see one of more beautiful Antioquia west
        views. Such as Rionegro, San Antonio de Pereira, Marinilla, Santuario, parte de Llano
        grande. \n\nContact: (+57) 311 396 62 94 - \n(57+4) 53819 27\nVereda San Ignacio sector Las Brisas</string>
    <string name="tiPpiedasblancas">POSADA PIDRAS BLANCAS</string>
    <string name="tPpidrasbancas">he Lodge Piedras Blancas has for about seven blocks of land, ideal
        to hiking, camping and picnic; where you can enjoy completely  by nature and little animals,
        shepherding, vegetable garden, fruit and wood trees, and native people. \n\n Contact:
        (+57) 312 417 7245 \nVereda Piedras Blancas. Sector El Tambo</string>
    <string name="tiMonasterio">EL MONASTERIO</string>
    <string name="tMonasterio">Thematic coffee, one of a kind. Natural tendency, author of kitchen
        oriented to patisserie. Rustic pizza is our specialty. This project is oriented to human
        wellness. Special birthdays and romantic dinners. In our Terrasana Farm has psychophysical
        sessions to meet again armory and equilibrium. Campfire, zoo-therapy , workshops, green
        days , mountain retreat. \n\nTeléfono:(57+4) 381089; (+57) 300-665-2553; (+57) 312 791 8163
        \n Main Road near central park</string>
    <string name="tiPlacebo">Placebo Coffee BAR</string>
    <string name="tPacebo">Good atmosphere, beautiful view, coffee, friends, place to be in the
        afternoons, grill, Bossa, boleros, Son Cuba, Rock, salsa, blues, tango music, art. Live music
        \n\nContact:(+57)315 521 4870 -(+57)305 225 8212 - (57+4) 538 0272 \nVereda El Placer</string>
    <string name="tiCiruela">Panaderia Ciruela</string>
    <string name="tCiruela">Ciruela Bakery is a warm and welcoming place where you find the richest
        aromas and the most delicious flavors of our fresh products. We enjoy your company in the
        making of the famous chocolate, seda and almond breads, blue cheese croissants, baguettes,
        cinnamon screws, pies, tarts, desserts and much more. \n\nTeléfono:
        (57+4)538 0437 - (57)320 775 8520 \nVereda El Plan, sector El Chispero</string>
    <string name="tiSilletas">Noche de Silletas</string>
    <string name="tSilletas">It is party time. A party is set up in Santa Elena the night before the
        Silleteros Parade. Thousands of tourists go about from vereda to vereda visiting the
        silleteras farms, to have a close look at the assembling of the silletas and to talk
        with the peasants about their culture and tradition.</string>
    <string name="tiAventura">Aventuras</string>
    <string name="tAventura">In Santa Elena is  lived the experience of:\n\nZip line: Flyover trees
        or a dam, feel the adrenaline and enjoy the landscape that you will discover on the tour.
        \n\nCycle tourism:The topography of the territory provides a perfect setting for bike touring,
        which offers routes of different levels, ranging from those appropriate for family excursions
        to specialized circuits for athletes. \n\nPaths and Trails: To walk through, catch the fresh
        air and contemplate the green landscape, this territory offers a series of paths amid the forest,
        suited for the enjoyment of birds, orchids, fauna and flora and also features several drivable
        circuits interconnecting different veredas and provided with somesightseeing interest.
        \n\nCanyoneering: Feel the adrenaline as you go down the emblematic waterfall of Santa Elena
        and other locations in the foggy forests.
    </string>
    <string name="tiArvi">Parque Arví</string>
    <string name="tArvi">It is an ecotourism park located  in the corregimiento Santa Elena, east of
        Medellín, created for the enjoyment of the whole local, national and international community,
        where they can enjoy trails, picnic areas, recreational parks as Comfama Arvi and Piedras
        Blancas, Arvi Market and travel on Metro Cable. It has 1761 hectares spread through the
        veredas Piedras Blancas, Mazo, Piedra Gorda and Barro Blanco, with plenty of foggy forests,
        one of the most important pieces of natural wealth of the territory, as it preserves the
        quality of the waters running down to the Valleys of Aburra and San Nicolas. Moreover, it
        constitutes the habitat for flowers, mosses, mushrooms, sarros, frogs, birds, butterflies and
        many other species of vital importance for the preservation of the forest.</string>
    <string name="tDemo">
According to the datas provided by the Statistical Yearbook of Medellín Santa Elena 2005,2 it has a
        population of about 10,898 inhabitants. It is the largest district of Medellin and has a
        density of 154 hab. By 2010 the population of over 12,000 inhabitants</string>
    <string name="tveredas1">The township has 11 Veredas</string>
    <string name="tveredas2">El Llano\n El Plan\n Media Luna\n Piedra Gorda</string>
    <string name="tveredas3">El Placer\nBarro Blanco\n La Palma\n Piedras Blancas-Matazano</string>
    <string name="tveredas4">Mazo\n El Cerro\n Santa Elena Sector Central</string>
    <string name="tAcerca">Sara Marcela Pavas Madrid\n c.c 1152687985\n sara.pavas@udea.edu.co\n Estudiante\n
    Programación para dispositivos móviles\n Ingeniería de Telecomunicaciones\n Universidad de Antioquia\n 2016</string>

</resources>